>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 当我们谈论功能时，我们可以变得更成熟
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We can get much more
sophisticated when we talk about function
参数和返回值。
parameters and return values.
您可以定义类似的定制类型。
You can define custom types like this.
我正在定义一个类型的对象，该对象具有名为 " 名称 " 的属性
Here I'm defining that an object of a type
that has a property called name that is
类型为字符串的类型。
of type string, that is a type.
然后，我可以将该类型的值作为参数传递。
And then I can pass values
of that type as parameters.
我可以将值作为参数接收回来。
And I can receive values
back as parameters.
所以我就在这个类型的学生的 studentRec 中。
So here I am passing in
studentRec of the type student.
如果你愿意我正在定义自己的类型
I'm defining my own type if you will.
因此，您可以定义这些定制类型更强大。
So it's much more powerful in that
you can define these custom types.
而这个程序，就是明确的，这个程序没有任何错误。
And this program, just to be clear,
this program doesn't have any errors.
因为它知道当我在第 4 行第 4 行返回 studentRec.name时，
Because what it knows is that when I
do line 4 a return of studentRec.name,
它知道 studentRec 是带有字符串的名称属性的对象。
it knows that studentRec was an object
with a name property that was string.
所以它知道它正在返回一个字符串
So it knows it's returning a string and
当第 9 行我尝试给它分配一个字符串它知道一切都很好
when line 9 I try to assign it
a string it knows everything is fine.
但你会注意到大部分的保证
But you'll notice that
most of the guarantee
这是正确分配的东西。
here is are things being
assigned correctly.
是否为他们分配了正确的类型 ?
Are they being assigned the right types?
函数的参数与变量类似。
A parameter to a function
is a lot like a variable.
如果你是说我只能通过数字
If you're saying I wanna only be
able to pass in numbers, then you're
就像我想要这个变量只保存数字一样
basically saying the same thing as I
want this variable to only hold numbers.
>> Kyle Simpson: 我要使用的内容如 typescript 我可能要定义
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Where I to uses something
like typescript I probably would define
我的很多参数都是工会的类型
many more of my parameters
as say union types.
或者我说，你知道，我要允许字符串，数字和空值。
Or I would say, you know what, I'm gonna
allow strings, numbers, and nulls.
因为难得的是我要它这么严格的
Because it's rare that I want it to be so
restrictive
例如，它只能接收到这种结构化对象。
that it can only ever receive exactly this
kind of structured object for example.
不过还是能做点有用的
But nevertheless,
it's able to do some very useful
保证您所遇到的问题是否为类型的错误分配。
guarantees if the problems that you
have are misassignments of types.